<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en-US" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://ledmyplace.ca/blogs/news.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://ledmyplace.ca/blogs/news"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://ledmyplace.ca/blogs/news.atom"/>
  <title>LEDMyplace Canada - News</title>
  <updated>2019-06-18T11:31:00-04:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>LEDMyplace Canada</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://ledmyplace.ca/blogs/news/the-benefits-of-led-lighting-you-should-know</id>
    <published>2019-06-18T11:31:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-06-18T11:34:00-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://ledmyplace.ca/blogs/news/the-benefits-of-led-lighting-you-should-know"/>
    <title>The Benefits of LED Lighting You Should Know</title>
    <author>
      <name>AJ Singh</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>LED lighting has a number of benefits in general when compared to traditional lighting. While LEDs provide improved energy and maintenance efficiencies as well as a better quality of light, there are also a few things they do for spaces such as parking lots and outdoor areas that many don’t embrace.<br><br>We have seen hundreds of businesses focus on indoor lighting and are constantly changing it, but they forget to focus on outdoor lights which usually consume more lighting energy.<br><br>LED Lights save energy and provide better light output than its conventional models.</p>
<h2>Lumen Output Control</h2>
<p>LEDs require LED-specific dimmer in order to function. Fortunately, this dimmer is readily available in the market, easy to install, and adds significant value to the overall lighting area lighting. In addition, the lifespan of the LEDs is significantly higher than the conventional bulbs. This allows facility managers to save even more money by managing lighting in an intelligent manner.</p>
<h2>Frequent Switching of LED Lights</h2>
<p>Unlike MH lights, LEDs can be turned ON instantaneously and turned back off with no zero error with respect to the lumen output. While metal halides or any other conventional bulb usually takes 12-15 minutes to get it back on. If there is a break of 30-45 minutes, you wouldn’t prefer to turn it off and turn it on since that would be a lot of hassle.</p>
<h2>LEDs Eliminate Warm-Up Times</h2>
<p>Metal Halide lamps, in particular, are infamous for long warm-up times (15-20 minutes is usual to work to full power). This is why you see large sports stadiums turn on the lights well before the sun’s light is completely gone. The stadium has to operate the lights for 20-25 minutes before they ever really need them to illuminate the stadium. That means they’re burning energy before they’re ever required.</p>
<h2>Wide beam angle is essential for uniform light output on a large area</h2>
<p>LED lights come with a strong infrastructure to illuminate a wider area which is not possible in case of traditional lighting. LED chips are equally spread in a designated pattern to release an equal amount of Lumens per watt around the area.<br><br>Achieving a uniform lumen output can actually give you an idea to purchase the exact number of fixtures for the area, which would lead you to save more energy and money with required LED lighting fixtures.<br><br>The minimum required beam angle for any fixture is required to be 120</p>
<h2>Up to you</h2>
<p>LED area lighting plays a vital in saving money on utility bills and energy simultaneously. At LEDMyplace Canada, we have our best selling categories - <a href="https://ledmyplace.ca/collections/led-tubes">LED Tubes</a>, <a href="https://ledmyplace.ca/collections/led-pole-lights">LED pole lights</a> &amp; <a href="https://ledmyplace.ca/collections/led-flood-lights">LED floodlights</a>. They perform the best when it comes to illuminating commercial, residential and industrial spaces.</p>
<p>Have you moved your area lighting to LED technology yet? Let us know in the comments.<br><br><br><br><br><br></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://ledmyplace.ca/blogs/news/why-led-tubes</id>
    <published>2019-06-04T12:32:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-06-18T02:07:13-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://ledmyplace.ca/blogs/news/why-led-tubes"/>
    <title>Why LED tubes?</title>
    <author>
      <name>Aindreas Cruse</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="LED Tubes" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/2242/2739/files/TUBE_IMAGE_grande.jpg?v=1559665957" style="float: none;"></p>
<p>LED Tubes have been dominating the lighting industry since its inception. No more swapping out the entire ballast, opting for an electronic over a magnetic one. Gone are the days of finding specific bulbs. No matter if your lighting is electronic or magnetic based, hybrid T8 LED tube lights are a viable solution.</p>
<p class="shoebox_blog">According to research, there are more than 1 billion fluorescent tubes in operation; thus, many homeowners and facility operators are motivated to find a more efficient solution.</p>
<p>Hybrid LED tubes are able to work with any existing lighting technology, whether it has an electronic ballast or magnetic ballast. Simply remove the existing fluorescent tube and pop in the new <a href="https://ledmyplace.ca/collections/led-tubes" title="LED Tube"><strong>LED tube</strong></a>. Voila. You’re finished.</p>
<h2>Drawbacks and benefits</h2>
<p>While the return on investment is a motivator for opting into the new technology, facility operators and homeowners should also consider these benefits:</p>
<p class="shoebox_blog">When installing the replacement tubes, the facility won’t experience downtime. All that’s required is that the installer turns off the light, snap out the tube and install the new one.</p>
<ul></ul>
<ul>
<li>They use less power.</li>
<li>They require less maintenance. You won’t need to hire a technician to install them, which is necessary for the old tube technology.</li>
<li>They don’t require rewiring. Formerly, you would need to remove the ballast to access a direct connection to the voltage.</li>
</ul>
<p class="shoebox_blog">Hybrid T8 LED tube lights are not without their downsides, however. Hybrid tubes are typically at the high-end range in terms of price and there is a concern regarding the ballast fittings in the light. However, LED lights to pay for themselves quickly in fixtures in which they’re used more than an hour or so a day (common in office settings where the tube lights are on all day). As a result, the payback period of LED lights is also decreasing. In many cases, the payback period can be as short as one year, or less than two to three years.</p>
<p>And in the Plug-n-play LED T8 tubes, we’ve tested, they’ve fit every ballast that has similar lighting currently in place.</p>
<h2 class="shoebox_blog"><strong>The spec</strong></h2>
<p>Light output. Hybrid LED tube lights emit a higher quality and brighter light as well as a variety of color variations. They also don’t flicker or produce that loud, familiar humming noise that older fluorescent emit.</p>
<p class="shoebox_blog">Life expectancy. LED light lifespan averages around 50,000 hours, with some models reaching 84,000. Compare these numbers to the old standard, where fluorescent lights lasted 30,000 hours.</p>
<p>Hybrid T8 LED tube lights are becoming the go-to choice for homeowners and facility operators seeking to best their bottom line. While a higher upfront cost is required, there are a host of benefits you’ll gain down the line. If you want to reduce downtime, lower maintenance costs and gain better lighting quality, these LED tube lights are the way to go.</p>
<h2>Conclusion</h2>
<p>LEDMyplace.ca is a one-stop online shop for all the LED lighting solution in Canada. While we are really proud of helping our customers find the best-LED lights in the market, we also make it important to support our customers to understand lighting technology and help them make self-decision.</p>
<p class="shoebox_blog">Have you installed LED tubes yet? Let us know in the comments</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://ledmyplace.ca/blogs/news/buy-ufo-led-high-bay-light-in-lowest-and-best-price-ledmyplace-ca</id>
    <published>2019-04-18T11:00:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-06-18T02:07:26-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://ledmyplace.ca/blogs/news/buy-ufo-led-high-bay-light-in-lowest-and-best-price-ledmyplace-ca"/>
    <title>Buy UFO LED High Bay Light in Lowest and Best Price - LEDMyplace.ca</title>
    <author>
      <name>AJ Singh</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>In this article, we will show some reasons why should you need to install UFO LED high bays. So read the whole article. <a href="https://ledmyplace.ca/collections/led-ufo-high-bay"><strong>UFO LED High Bay</strong></a> lights are intended to supplant Metal Halide of 250W to 2000W, High Weight Sodium and fluorescent high lights in roofs 15-plus feet high.</p>
<p><strong>LED UFO High Bay Lights</strong></p>
<p>While choosing light installations for high inlet applications, the most critical thing is proficiency. Since the light apparatuses will illuminate the space from a high point, the light should be advanced for enlightenment. UFO high bayous have a one of a kind plan that assumes an essential job in their effectiveness. Their gigantic UFO style warm sink guarantees they exchange warm properties all the more equally and effectively. Models are accessible to supplant 250W, 400W and 1000W Stowed away.</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/2242/2739/files/ufo_1_large.jpg?v=1555599442" alt="UFO High Bay LED Light" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p>These lights give light that is ground-breaking and also uniform. They are great developed and have Ingress Protection 65 rating, which means they can be introduced in unforgiving conditions and still function admirably. These lights are likewise either UL or ETL Recorded for wellbeing purposes and DLC qualified, which implies you might almost certainly get a discount from your service organization.</p>
<p>One thing UFO Drove Inlet light installations do well is consolidate usefulness with style. At the point when introduced in a space, they upgrade its style due to their striking appearance. These light apparatuses are perfect for high straight applications that require wonderful and useful light.</p>
<p><strong>Reason 1: These UFO lights are tough apparatuses</strong> <br> <br> UFO Light Emitting Diode High bay apparatuses can withstand outrageous cold and hot temperatures or as far as possible up to 87.77 degrees Celsius, without diminishing its life expectancy. This is conceivable through our vast warmth sinks, uniquely intended to keep the lights cool. Their installations are additionally vibration safe, enabling them to keep up a long life expectancy, ideal for business and modern conditions requiring mechanical high cove drove lighting apparatuses.</p>
<p><strong>Reason 2: Effectively supplant UFO LED T5 high yield fluorescent installations</strong> <br> <br> Are you tired of evolving tubes? Also tired of CFL tube lights that don't keep going as long as they should? Supplanting T5 HO Fluorescent installations is basic and simple. Each T5 tube creates roughly 4000 lumens each. The light isn't directional, so compelling lumens is in reality not exactly the 24000 consolidated lumens for a 6 tube installation. You can without much of a stretch supplant these apparatuses with a practical, upkeep free proportional Drove arrangement.</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/2242/2739/files/ufo_large.jpg?v=1555599494" alt="UFO High Bay LED Light" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p><strong>Reason 3: UFO LED High Bays requires fewer maintenance expenses</strong><br> <br> LED UFO High Bays are L70 evaluated last upwards of 100,000+ hours. This takes into account fewer substitutions of your narrows installations, which is exorbitant in applications, for example, a manufacturing plant or distribution centre where high straight lights are utilized because of the outrageous statures they are introduced at. Cost saver of Drove high narrows light installations is regularly neglected, however spares a gigantic measure of cash.</p>
<p><strong>Reason 4: Ingress Protection evaluate high</strong>  <br> <br> A considerable lot of your business LED UFO high bay lights apparatuses are planned with an Ingress Protection evaluating. Ingress Protection is a rating framework that decides how well an apparatus can keep out residue and dampness. It is spoken to as IPXX, where the main digit is the means by which well it keeps out residue and the second digit discusses by which well it keeps out water.</p>
<p><strong>Reason 5: High temperature evaluated alternatives</strong> <br> <br> UFO LED (Light Emitting Diode) High bays that are appraised for encompassing temperatures for 140F, 150F, 176F and even 194F. These bays are designed to last, and a significant number of them can be arranged to be either introduced as a flood light.</p>
<p><strong>Reason 6: High voltage for 100v-277v, 277v-480v or much higher on the off chance that you need</strong></p>
<p><br> It is safe to say that you are attempting to supplant high straight installations that are 277V? 347V? 480V? We have arrangements that cover these higher voltage establishments. Steady momentum drivers are prepared to deal from 100V-277V or 377V-480V. We can deal with single or 3-stage control also.</p>
<p><strong>Reason 7: UFO LED High Bays will decrease your lighting Expenses by approximately 70%</strong> <br> <br> Diminishing business high straight lighting expenses winds up useful and supportable with our vitality effective indoor high cove lights. With vitality reserve funds up to 70%, you can diminish a gigantic measure of vitality utilization. Likewise, spare with UFO LED (Light Emitting Diode) high narrows through longer life expectancies, motion sensors, decreased upkeep costs, dimmable high inlet lighting choices, and even refunds.</p>
<p><strong>Reason 8: Its Lumen Intensity</strong><br>  <br> The modernization of the present light source has made an impressive enhancement in vitality effectiveness. On account of the imaginative advancements in the lighting business, for example, the utilization of Drove, and controls that work with these lights, lighting items are currently progressively productive and vitality utilization has gone down considerably. This converts into a vast decrease in the expense of lighting.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
</feed>
